worldsings.com 2011-05-10

# WORLDSINGS - The Global Home For Music

Privacy Policy

 **Effective: August 1, 2008**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how WorldSings (“Site”) collects, uses and shares the personal information (“PI”) that registered users (“Members”) voluntarily provide when they register. The term “User” as used herein, refers to both Members and unregistered users (“Visitors”). This Policy applies to all Users with respect to any of the services offered by WorldSings, including discussion groups, blogs, messaging, forums, contests and any other feature or content offered by WorldSings in connection with this web site (collectively “Services”).

**How information is collected**  
WorldSings collects two types of User information: Personal information (“PI”) that Users voluntarily provide when they become registered users, and web site use information (“UI”) that is collected every time a User visits or interacts with this site. PI includes information such as the Users full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number and all other information that a User provides by voluntarily responding to a request from WorldSings or its affiliates. UI is information that is electronically gathered when Users enter the web site, such as your browser type, IP address and aggregate user data. This data is primarily used to manage and improve the Services and the site, track usage and for security purposes.

Users may also provide Non-personal Information (“NPI”), some of which is collected by WorldSings, while some of it is not. For example, when Members vote for their favorite song or entry in the “WorldSingsTM World’s Best Song” contest (“Contest”), this information is collected by WorldSings, but is not treated as personal information. On the other hand, users may post comments, and provide information on their Profile pages including, but not limited to hobbies, interests, education, lifestyle, date of birth, pictures and links to Third Party Sites. This information is not requested by WorldSings and is not collected and Users provide this information at their sole discretion.

Members may change their registration PI and Profile page information at any time.

Cookies: Cookies are small bits of data that are stored on the User’s computer and are tied to information about the User. Cookies are used to identify the User’s preferences, identify their internet browser, authenticate the user and other uses tied with your use of the web site. Your browser preferences allow you to control Cookies on your computer. However, if you choose to block all Cookies, you may be unable to access certain features of the site. Additionally, third parties that advertise on WorldSings may also contain Cookies. WorldSings does not control these third party cookies and Users must check the privacy policy of the third party to see whether and how it uses cookies.

**How information is used**  
Except as described in this Policy, WorldSings will not share your PI with third parties that are not affiliated with WorldSings unless you give WorldSings permission to do so. WorldSings may share NPI with third parties to provide relevant services and advertisements to Members. WorldSings may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by WorldSings that we think you may be interested in.

Invitations and messages sent via email addresses are used for the purpose of inviting new friends to join WorldSings, add users to existing Member networks and send notifications. When you invite another person, and that person accepts the invitation, WorldSings will ask for that person’s name and information. While email addresses are not displayed or shared with people in your Member network and User’s full names are not directly revealed to other Members, WorldSings Users are able to search for other Members using search criteria found in the Member’s profile, including names and email addresses.

Cookies may also be used to customize the content and advertising you receive based on your Profile information and other information you provide. For example, based on your music interests, including which songs you vote for in the Contest, WorldSings might display an advertisement or otherwise provide you with information of interest regarding your music interest, such as upcoming concerts, new music releases and events.

If you have consented to receiving promotional or advertising material from WorldSings, WorldSings may use your email address to send that information to you. Users have the option to unsubscribe to any email service by changing the Profile information.

**Security**  
WorldSings uses commercially reasonable measures to safeguard PI, including credit card information in its possession from theft, loss, disclosure or unauthorized use. All information is located on a secure server behind a firewall. Sensitive information such as passwords and credit card numbers are encrypted for your protection. WorldSings employees, agents and contractors must have a genuine business reason to obtain access to your PI.

**Disclosure Policy**  
WorldSings is committed to your online privacy. However, there may be occasions where WorldSings may access or disclose PI in order to: 1) satisfy any applicable law, search warrant, subpoena, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, 2) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations of the Terms of Use, 3) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, and 4) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of WorldSings, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**User Responsibilities**  
Users are encouraged to safeguard the privacy of their PI. Users should not share or post PI on their Profile pages, including social security numbers, telephone numbers, addresses, passwords, and credit card numbers. WorldSings does not and is not obligated to monitor Profile pages to determine whether Users have voluntarily disclosed personal information.

**Notice, Revisions and Contact Information**  
All uses of WorldSings are subject to this Policy in addition to the Terms of Use. This Policy is current as of the “Effective” date appearing at the top of the Policy. WorldSings may modify this Policy periodically and any such modifications will be effective upon posting the revised Policy to this site. Users should read this Policy and periodically check for updates as your continued use of this site signifies your acceptance of the revised Policy.

**WorldSings does not knowingly collect any PI from children under 13 years of age.**

Any questions regarding this Policy including WorldSings collection and use of your personal information may be directed to:  
Or by mail to:  
WorldSings.com, LLC.  
P.O. Box 11491  
Burbank, CA 91510
